Even after getting his ass handed to him,
that Hazamada guy still
said he didn't know
anything about that Sparky
SOB who killed my bro?
Yeah, apparently he's only ever
talked to him over the phone.
You did torture that twat waffle
before he told you this, right?
He could have been lying to you!
Look, I really believe Hazamada
was telling me the truth.
If he knew the user's identity,
he would have been killed by now.
Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
That is why my bro was offed.
Exactly.
And Hazemada's still breathing, isn't he?
For now, that's all the proof we
need that he's telling the truth.
Now then, Hazamada did
tell us about one thing.
Don't ask me to tell you why this is?
But it seems Stan users are
inadvertently drawn to each other,
even if the users have never
laid eyes on one another.
You've heard of the myth
that says the red thread
of fate forever connects
you with your partner-to-be,
right?
Like in the myth, Stan users
are bound to cross paths.
The user could be an enemy a friend that
annoying guy on the bus who steps on your
foot or even your new next door neighbor
everyone is suspect morio's a small town
you know it's anybody's
guess how many stan
users are living here but tries they made
to conceal themselves they'll eventually
emerge he knows it's just a matter of time
before destiny brings you together so he
wants you to disappear before that happens
damn it this shithead's a damn coward
what the hell is he waiting for well he's
probably playing it safe for the time being
when guys like that decide to go on the
offensive it's usually because they're
confident that no one can take them I'm out.
Huh?
Hey, it's Koichi!
Yeah, but why is he at a snooty cafe?
Yoo-hoo! Koichi!
What?!
What the?!
Josuke, it's the girl!
Thank you.
Mr.
Week
So, Koichi, I hope
meeting me here wasn't...
too much trouble. Huh?
It wasn't any trouble at all.
Really, there's nowhere
else I'd rather be.
Although I'm not quite
sure what this is about.
Wow, Koichi's actually with a girl.
And not just any girl.
That's you, Kick Yamagishi, from my class!
Come on, let's get a closer look!
I'm not sure if this is about
showing you my homework,
but you should probably
know my grades aren't
all that good and my handwriting's sloppy.
Though if it's money,
I suppose I could give you a thousand yen,
or maybe you came here to ask me
to be the weekly class leader.
I'm afraid it's none of
those. Really? It isn't?
Then why did you want to meet me here?
If you're looking for someone
to take in a kitten or puppy,
I'm sorry to say I already
have a dopey dog named police.
Koichi, I...
I have to tell you something.
Koichi, you need to know that I've
fallen madly in love with you!
What did she say?!
I'm sorry, I don't
think I heard you right.
I'm sure you did.
Every day all I think
about is you, Koichi.
I've been oh so frightened
to utter those words to you.
However, if I held it in any
longer, my heart was going to burst.
But I had to take a leap.
And tell you my true feelings
even if you were to hate me.
Is this really happening?
Is she actually professing her love to me?
I wouldn't believe it if I hadn't
heard it, but that's what she said!
I'm so happy!
Josuke, please tell me
this isn't happening!
Why does Koichi get all the luck?
No one's ever said anything
like that to me before!
There you big baby.
There's no need to cry, but still holy
crap that Koichi sure is something
So Koichi, you must have
a girlfriend already.
No, I'm as single as can be
Hang on.
You wouldn't tease me
about something like this.
Would you? No way. I'm serious.
I Noticed your face has become
more chiseled as of late?
A strong face brimming with
courage and conviction!
Also, you're really
charming when you smile.
You know, she's honestly
making a lot of good points.
I have a chiseled face too, don't I?
That said, what attracts me to a man
more than anything else is potential.
And you are potential personified.
Wow, that's the first time
anyone's ever said that to me.
But you must be repulsed
by homely girls like me.
I don't blame you.
What are you talking about?
That's not how I see you at all.
Would you come on, you lucky bastard?
Quit messing around and seal
the deal with that hottie.
Just go for it and ask her out already!
Please be honest.
Do you hate me?
No, don't be ridiculous.
I couldn't hate you even if I wanted to.
Do you love me?
Hold on a second.
Don't you think we're
moving a bit too fast?
You do hate me.
No, you've got it all wrong.
You just caught me off guard when
you started talking about love.
Well, which is it?
Are you madly in love or
toying with my feelings?
Answer me, dammit!
I poured my heart out to you!
And now I've spilled my coffee!
All because of your heartlessness!
I don't know what just came over me.
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me!
Goodbye.
You'll come see me again, I hope.
Well, I have to say, for some reason, I
suddenly feel like a deflated balloon.
Any jealousy I had over that just
went right out of the window.
No kidding.
Let's pretend we didn't see any of that.
Yeah.
What's with my cola?
Why's all this hair in it?
What in the world is going on?
Stand users are always
drawn to each other, huh?
Could it be?
Hey, it's me, Koichi.
Oh no! Oh, Yukako!
What are you doing?
Well, uh, it's my turn to clean the
lab so I'm doing my part to help out.
Fourth period was
chemistry lab, after all.
Koichi.
About yesterday, I know I
said some strange things,
but I hope you'll forget all that.
I have a bad habit of behaving
that way when I overthink things.
I'm so embarrassed.
How could I forget how important
it is to be open-minded?
That's true, but don't worry.
You surprised me a little
bit, but it's no big deal.
I don't think any less of you.
We can still be friends despite
my outburst, right? Of course!
That works for me!
I'd love to be friends with you!
Really? Thank goodness!
I was so worried that
you absolutely hated me!
I was tossing and turning all night!
Well, that's just silly!
And as a little something to show
you just how sorry I am. Here!
I so hope you like it!
I spent the whole night
knitting this for you!
And what a relief!
I knew your length and chest width,
but I had a guess about the
shoulders and it fits perfectly!
I made you an amulet too!
Now you can find true love!
And there's more!
I also made us Bind boxes!
Everything we need to have lunch together!
I bought the shrimp at the
local market this morning!
You won't find freshness
like this at a grocery store!
This is Flounder Minoru, but I made sure
to remove every single bone with tweezers!
Now open wide, please!
As if yesterday wasn't enough.
This is definitive proof that Yukako
Yamagishi is completely deranged.
I've got to put a stop to this.
But if I take a bite, I'll
just validate her feelings.
And if I refuse, she'll kill me.
What am I supposed to do?
Come on, Hirose.
Quit goofing off, slacker.
Class is going to be starting any minute,
so hurry up and dump this garbage.
Yes, thank God for trash.
Oh, yeah, how could I have forgotten?
I'll take care of this right now!
Geez, you are totally hopeless!
Here, just give it to me.
I'll take it outside for you.
No, it's fine. I've got it.
Just hand it over, would ya?
I'm the class rep, so I'm the
one who's gonna get chewed out.
Geez.
Sorry.
Hey you huh I'll ask you one time to
stop flirting with Koichi what are you
talking about do you mean Koichi Hirose
you're joking right I don't know what
you've heard but there's nothing going
on with us that pathetic lie might have
worked on me if you didn't reek with
the stench of a Malodorous homewrecker.
A what?
The hell are you talking about?
Listen closely.
If I catch you trying
to seduce Koichi again,
mark my words, I'll make
your life a living hell.
You hold your horses, bitch.
You're threatening me over
a spindly scrub like Koichi?
I couldn't give two shits about the guy.
Even if I was all into him, you
have absolutely no right to tell me?
what I can or cannot do, dumbass!
Man, that hurt. What happened?
What the hell is her problem?
That psycho is out of her mind.
She has the hots for Koichi.
Huh, what a joke.
Just wait until the school finds out.
Huh?
Wait, what's that?
I feel hot.
Something's not right.
What's going on?
It feels like I'm burning up.
Water!
Someone help me! Water!
I need water!
I'm so sorry!
Hey Josuke!
Looks like you were right about
Yukakoyama Gishi being a stand user.
It's a stand that manipulates
hair at will! Seems like.
But given what we've seen,
it doesn't appear as though she'd go
after Koichi or us for that matter.
Anyway, Okuyasu, what are you planning
to do about this girl's messed up hair?
I'm not sure if you know this,
but Shining Diamond isn't able
to fix stuff the hand takes away.
Huh?
Haven't I done enough for one day?
I did keep her from
getting burned to a crisp.
Even if I wanted to do something,
I'm not much of a hair stylist.
Huh.
Oh no, what am I gonna do?
Look what I got on my
latest English test. Whoa.
Yukako has been stressing me out so
much I haven't been able to concentrate.
Oh man, even I did better than you did.
I got a 32 on that test.
If I'm being honest,
when she started paying attention to me,
I was a little excited about
where things were going.
I mean, no girl's ever
said she loved me before.
Yeah, I totally feel what you're
saying on that one, my man.
I feel you deeply. Mm-hmm.
I was way too wishy-washy about my feelings
and brought this all on myself, darn it!
There's only one way to
end this madness now!
I have to tell Yukako that I'm not
interested in her, so she leaves me alone!
I'd think twice about that, Koichi.
If you try being that blunt with her,
it'll only fan the demented
flames of her passion even more.
She'll lose it again.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Well, of course I'm right.
Now listen up.
Yukako is insane,
but convincing her to stop using
her hair for evil is low priority.
We have far more pressing
concerns at the moment.
Figuring out a way to not
provoke her comes first.
But how do we do that?
The truth is, it doesn't matter
how infatuated she is with you.
If she comes to her own conclusion
that you're the most pathetic,
disgusting schmuck around, then we get to
go on living happily ever after, right?
So all you've got to do
on your end is act like
a total jackass whenever
you're in front of her.
Oh, now I get where
you're going with this.
You're such a genius, Josuke.
Well, thank you.
Though is it really a
compliment coming from you?
Jeez, Luis, what could I do to make
Yukako think I'm totally unappealing?
Well,
from what I've been told,
mama's boys and gross guys are
usually major turn-offs for ladies.
There has to be another way!
If she thinks I'm a mama's boy, she'll
hate my mom and go after her, too!
Then we'll have to go with option B!
You'll be the gross guy
who doesn't take baths!
That's right.
You can't brush your teeth
or change your underwear.
Raising some lice or spiders in
your hair might be a good idea!
Wearing sweaty socks is pretty gross!
Ooh, and try farting everywhere!
Yeah, she'll think you're foul!
Would you guys quit joking?
Around I'm serious about
this I'm being just as
serious as you are now make
with the snot and drool.
If you're not up for it
then your only option is
to become a nobody and a
nobody with no prospects?
At that you need to make
her lose all interests
you and I are going to tackle
this thing together. Okay?
Holy shit! No way!
Koichi Hirose did what?
I don't believe it!
How disgusting does a guy have
to be to stoop to shoplifting?
I know, but Koichi said it himself!
What's worse, the jerk was
even bragging all about it!
Who does that?
Think that's bad?
Koichi wouldn't be able to keep a
promise if his life depended on it!
I lent that asshat money
and he never paid me back!
Yeah, well, I heard he cheats on
tests and steals girls' underwear.
The guy's got no future.
He'll end up ruining his life.
I think it's time to drop the dude.
Our friendship is over.
Oh, man, that chick gives
Intense a new definition.
Now, if Koichi can confirm tomorrow
all the stuff we said today,
she'll lose interest faster than
a lead block fallen from the sky.
I know I should have faith in them,
but I wonder if Josuke
and Okuyasu's plan worked.
The best-case scenario would be her
forgetting that I exist altogether.
What is that?
My eyes are closed, so it must be a dream.
Huh?
A woman?
It's Yukako!
You have to be kidding me!
She's even corrupting my dreams?
Can't she give it a rest for one night?
Ah!
I hate to do this, Koichi!
but I have to tell you, your friends
don't think very highly of you.
No need to worry, I'm here for you now.
And as such, it's my job to educate
you and turn you into the ideal man.
There's something about you?
Certain other men seem to be lacking,
and it's crucial that you
live up to that potential.
Josuke!
The plan backfired big time!
What is this place?
Koichi, are you hungry now?
Breakfast is almost ready, okay?
Yeah, okay.
I have to remember that
she has that hair stand.
There's no fighting it, so I
have to find an opening and run.
It's my only hope.
Hey, I have a question.
Can you answer it? I'll try.
Well, it's about what
your hair did last night.
How did you do that?
Were you surprised?
Silly me.
I suppose the first time
would startle anyone.
It was around February.
Somebody shot an arrow into my chest.
Though, it's possible I was dreaming it.
When I woke up, it was as if my wound
never existed, and I had this power.
Keicho Nijimura!
So, do you know anyone else with
special powers like yours? No.
That means she has no
idea I'm a stand user too!
Have a seat if you would.
You are a growing boy, right?
But if you don't eat properly,
you'll never become the outstanding
man I know you can be. Crap.
I've got to play along for now.
This looks amazing! Oh, boy!
Not so fast, mister.
We need to talk. Huh?
You failed your English test.
While I acknowledge there's more
to a man than his intelligence,
this pitiful score is unacceptable.
To prepare you for the next test, You're
going to study while you eat breakfast,
okay?
Now, for a few questions.
Select the best answer
from among the boxes.
The box you choose holds your next meal.
Wait, hold on a minute.
You'll do what I say.
And as long as you're
living in this house,
your life must constantly
revolve around your betterment.
Agreed?
On to the question.
In Prince's lyrics,
he uses the words funky music and I
want the best Japanese translation. A.
Nekkyō no ongaku. B.
Genshi no ongaku. C.
Gensou no ongaku.
If I don't answer her question,
she'll get hysterical!
But I don't have a flippin' clue!
I have a hunch it's A, but it
could easily be B or C as well!
Tch...screw it!
I can do this!
Tch...my guess is... B!
You got it right!
Congratulations!
You won a pair of
freshly hard-boiled eggs!
I'll peel them for you with
a pinch of salt, right?
Just so you know, if you had chosen A,
you would have had to eat this eraser.
Box C would have been a bar of soap.
What the hell?!
The next item on the
menu is bacon and eggs.
Best of luck!
Your question.
Which of these characters
express contrast?
Would it be Dish A, perhaps
Dish B, or maybe Dish C?
She's not messing around here.
If I choose the wrong box, she'll
force me to eat its contents for sure!
I know you're stalling for time.
Hurry or your food will get cold.
Uh, well...
Maybe it's...
What do I do now?
She's playing hardball!
Hm.
Duh! Hm.
Duh! Is... Itsy?
Tell me, Koichi.
Were you watching my expressions
to decide which box to pick? Duh!
I never thought I'd say this,
but your reputation for being a
conniving shoplifting traitor is true!
For your penalty, you shall consume
the contents of boxes A and B!
A is English vocab Corn Flakes.
B is asparagus a la English dictionary.
You're gonna learn with
every bite you take.
Here, now open up that mouth,
because here comes the knowledge.
What's wrong?
Eat your food, dammit!
I've had about enough of this.
You expect me to sit
back and take this crap?
Well, I can't.
I'm getting the hell out of here.
Now what's happening?
What's pulling my scalp?
It feels like somebody's hair.
Wait, does this belong to?
Indeed, I implanted a few hundred
strands of my own hair into your scalp.
I'm well aware that you'll probably hate
me for going to these extreme measures,
Koichi.
But by the time you leave this house,
you'll look in the mirror and see a
brand new man staring back at you.
I'm certain you'll thank me after that.
And and you'll realize you need
a woman like me in your life.
It's safe to say you won't be able
to live without Yukako Yamagishi.
Oh, you might as well know.
Until you finish every
last morsel on your plates,
I won't be giving you any more food.
There's one more thing.
A famous CEO vacations here, but no
one will be visiting until summer.
Until summer?!
Although, it doesn't
really matter who drops by,
Because, in the very end,
love is an invincible power.
Somebody help me!